ipipeline.com 2013-10-19

# iPipeline - integrated solutions for the Insurance & Financial Services Industry

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement Effective as of April 12, 2007**

Internet Pipeline, Inc. ("iPipeline", "we", "our" or "us") has created this privacy statement ("Statement") in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the iPipeline web site (the "Site") is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our users, we have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. This policy only applies to http://netrac.ipipeline.com, http://igoforms.ipipeline.com, www.ipipeline.com, and www.myagency.net and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. We reserve the right to change this Statement and will provide notification, through the Site, of the change at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.

The Privacy Statement is designed and targeted to U.S. audiences and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U.S. We make no representation that our Website is operated in accordance with the laws or governed by other nations. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the U.S. and you use our Website contrary to the terms and conditions of the Agreement or the laws, regulations, treaties and legal requirements of the United States or that otherwise apply to you in your country, community and legal governing jurisdiction (the "Law"), you do so at your own risk. You, not us, are responsible for compliance with the Law that applies to you.

**Our Contact Information**  
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy.

Our internet address is located at [http://www.ipipeline.com](http://www.ipipeline.com/).

**Our business address is:  
iPipeline  
222 Valley Creek Blvd., Suite 300  
Exton, PA 19341**

You may contact us by e-mail at [privacy@iPipeline.com](mailto:privacy@iPipeline.com).

**Personal Information We Collect**

We provide services through our Site which allows users to enter information about themselves or on behalf of clients or other third parties. Such information may include non-public personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") including contact information, family information, financial information and health information. Examples of such information which we may collect include, but is not limited to, a user, client or third party's: first name, last name, home address, business address, phone number, e-mail address, drivers license number, social security number, age, title, income, net worth, credit card information, business information, trust information, estate information, financial institution information, weight, height, income, insurance, medical history, family history or any other information which may be requested for an insurance policy.

Users entering Personal Information through the Site hereby certify to us that you have complied with all laws, rules or regulations, including, without limitation, the Gramm-Leach- Bliley Act ("GLB"), the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act ("HIPAA"), the FTC Privacy Rule and applicable state privacy disclosure laws ("Privacy Laws"). You further certify that any consumer or customer whose information may be inputted, submitted to, and/or appear on this Site has given you the authorization to convey this information to and through our Site and for further conveyance to certain other entities. Moreover, you understand and certify that we are relying upon this representation in allowing you access and use our Site and that if you have in any way failed to comply with any Privacy Laws that we would not have permitted to you access and use our Site.

**Use of Personal Information**

The iGOFORMS Site collects user and client information on behalf of insurance companies and other third parties to complete online insurance applications and other forms. A UserID and password is used to display the correct content within the Site. Personal Information collected on the Site is stored in an encrypted database and not used for marketing nor solicitation purposes by us. 

We may also access and use any Personal Information provided by you in order to perform any services which you request through the Site and, if necessary, to access such information to obtain contact information in order to provide notifications relating to these services to you. 

We may also access and use any Personal Information provided by you in order to perform any services which you request through the Site and, if necessary, to access such information to obtain contact information in order to provide notifications relating to these services to you. We may also collect certain information from users of the Site, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Service. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our users and provide such information to third parties. 

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Our Site allows the user to print the information collected. Our Site also allows a user to submit and transmit the Personal Information to third parties through secure channels. Third parties include: insurance companies, brokerage general agencies, insurance agencies, paramedical companies, insurance technology vendors, and other parties who may provide services for the purpose for which the data was entered and transmitted. 

**Retention of Personal Information**

We shall retain Personal Information in accordance with federal, state and local laws, rules and regulations. 

**Updating Personal Information**

Personal Information may be updated by the user entering the Site with a valid UserID and password and modifying the information on the Site. However, any Personal Information which has been electronically signed or submitted through the system may not be changed or deleted. 

**Cookies**

When you interact with the Site we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. When you come to our Web site, our Web server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are files that Web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to tell us whether customers and visitors have visited the Site previously. 

Standing alone, cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you've closed your browser or turned off your computer. They include such information as a unique identifier for your browser. 

We use session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows us to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you've logged in and are required in order to use our application. We use persistent cookies, that only we can read and use, to identify the fact that you are our user or prior Site visitor (whatever the case may be). We are especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, we do not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. Users who disable their Web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our Website but will not be able to successfully use our Service. 

**Third Party Cookies**

We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our website to help us administer our website and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual website visitors to any personally identifiable information. All data collected by such third parties on behalf of iPipeline is used only to provide us with information on site usage and is not shared with any other third parties. 

**Third-Party Sites**

The Site may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. Users will need to check the policy statement of these others web sites to understand their policies. Users who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.

**Security**

Our Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Personal Information under our control. When our Site is accessed using Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.5 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that your Personal Information is safe, secure, and available only to you. We also implement an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and host the Site in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, we provide unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a user logs on (unless you are entering the system through another trusted website). These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of Personal Information. 

Users are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their UserID and password.

**Opt-Out Policy**

If, at any time after using the service, you change your mind about sharing your information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to [privacy@iPipeline.com](mailto:privacy@iPipeline.com).
